iconeden.com 2011-05-18

# Legal - Icon Eden

## Terms of Service

By using the IconEden.com service ("Service") of Frexy Studio, you are agreeing to be bound by the following terms and conditions ("Terms Of Service") and our privacy policy. You are advised to check the Privacy Policy from time to time for any updates or changes that may impact you. 

#### General Conditions

  1. We reserve the right to modify or terminate the Service for any reason, with or without notice at any time.
  2. We reserve the right to refuse Service to anyone for any reason at any time.
  3. We reserve the right to change fees charges for products and services for any reason, with or without notice at any time.
  4. Your use of the Service is at your own risk. The Service is provided on an "as is" and "as available" basis without any warranty or condition, express, implied or statutory.
  5. Frexy Studio does not warrant that the service will be uninterrupted, timely or error-free.
  6. Any questions regarding the Terms Of Service shall be e-mailed to info [-at-] iconeden [-dot-] com. 

#### Payment and Access

  1. All payments are handled by [2Checkout.com](http://www.2checkout.com/). Frexy Studio may not be held liable for any damage during the payment progress on the 2Checkout.com website. 
  2. All fees are exclusive of all taxes, levies, or duties imposed by taxing authorities, and you shall be responsible for payment of all such taxes, levies or duties. 

#### Copyright and Ownership

  1. All content is copyright © Frexy Studio.
  2. You agree not to reproduce, duplicate, copy, sell, resell or exploit any portion of the Service, use of the Service, or access to the Service without the express written permission by Frexy Studio.
  3. You are not allowed to share the content with anyone except the ways that are described in the additional agreement.

## Privacy Policy

Frexy Studio respects each individual’s right to personal privacy. We will collect and use information through IconEden.com website only in the ways disclosed in this statement. This statement applies solely to information collected at IconEden.com website.

#### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you place an order or fill out a form. When ordering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, files (if any). Like most websites, we use cookies to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visit to our website. Please refer to the ’Do we use cookies?’ section below for more information about cookies and how we use them. 

#### What do we use your information for

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * ##### To handle transactions

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. 
  * ##### To send periodic e-mails

The e-mail address you provide for order processing will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. 

#### How do we protect your information?

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway provider’s database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

#### Do we use cookies?

No. You are absolutely free from them. If any, they are [session cookies](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Session_\(computer_science\)#HTTP_session_token) that are automatically cleared any time your browser is closed. 

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

#### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section regarding account, payment and access, copyright and ownership. 

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update our privacy modification date as below.

This policy was last modified on September 30, 2008.

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us via info [-at-] iconeden [-dot-] com

### Return Policy

This is Frexy Studio’s Return Policy. Please read carefully before completing your purchase.

We work mainly in the digital format. The product you purchase or license from us is made up of little colored dots called pixels. These little bits of data are extremely easy to copy and send around to all your friends. They are also impossible to return, the way that traditional physical products, like shoes, toys, ect., can be returned. We cannot possibly know what happens to our digital content once you pay for and download it. Therefore, we cannot refund purchases of digital content, except in the following cases:

  * ##### Partial return

The content in question is not at all what you were taking use of and you therefore may request a partial refund for any items that have not yet been worked on, you have not made copies of it nor sent it to anyone, and are willing to put that all in writing. 
  * ##### Full return

The content in question is not at all what you were expecting and you therefore cannot use it, you have not made copies of it nor sent it to anyone, and are willing to put that all in writing. 

If you do wish to request a refund, please contact us within 24 hours of the transaction in question. Requests for refunds later than 24 hours after the transaction in question may not be honored and shall remain at our discretion. 

In ANY case, in order to initiate the refund process, we require that you contact us first, via email, and try to resolve any issues with us directly, before contacting your credit card company. Unless we have a record of a conversation or correspondence with you regarding a request for a refund, we cannot authorize the refund of transactions previously completed. We reserve the right not to accept your request for a refund if you do not follow this protocol. We typically respond to inquiries within 5 business days. We reserve the right to refuse a refund we believe is based on a fraudulent claim. 

However, we do care very much that you are satisfied with the content you have purchased, so if you have any difficulties, concerns, or questions, please send email to us at sales [-at-] iconeden [-dot-] com.
